[{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "60b889b06a02f51e3cca53b0"
  },
  "userId": "673hgf-7645u83-87653uf84449",
  "batchId": "10002",
  "timeAttendant": {
    "$date": "2021-06-03T07:50:08.554Z"
  },
  "attended": true,
  "comment": "Can Focus on Improving Backend",
  "rating": [
    {
      "_id": {
        "$oid": "60b889b06a02f51e3cca53b1"
      },
      "question": "How was the Listening",
      "answer": 16,
      "id": "b93731f6-f44b-4021-a214-be40b34a2ac2"
    },
    {
      "_id": {
        "$oid": "60b889b06a02f51e3cca53b2"
      },
      "question": "How was the Speaking Skills",
      "answer": 9,
      "id": "2d51cbb4-d079-4d4c-9608-4d8e8124d2bd"
    },
    {
      "_id": {
        "$oid": "60b889b06a02f51e3cca53b3"
      },
      "question": "Any Improvement required",
      "answer": 8,
      "id": "46d42d48-7cf8-4364-85d0-de3d679677f4"
    },
    {
      "_id": {
        "$oid": "60b889b06a02f51e3cca53b4"
      },
      "question": "How was the Concentration of Child",
      "answer": 7,
      "id": "0ecf8f66-657f-4d99-99c8-bc35ebd40d5d"
    },
    {
      "_id": {
        "$oid": "60b889b06a02f51e3cca53b5"
      },
      "question": "How was the Level of Knowledge Gained",
      "answer": 9,
      "id": "c3945878-6e6d-44b0-9c92-bc52b1590e63"
    }
  ],
  "id": "4ad21145-71f8-4c14-9941-5d3408722e3b",
  "__v": 0
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "60b889fe6a02f51e3cca53c2"
  },
  "userId": "673hgf-7645u83-87653uf84449",
  "batchId": "10002",
  "timeAttendant": {
    "$date": "2021-06-03T07:51:26.474Z"
  },
  "attended": true,
  "comment": "we",
  "rating": [
    {
      "_id": {
        "$oid": "60b889fe6a02f51e3cca53c3"
      },
      "question": "e",
      "answer": 2,
      "id": "da924e7d-fcfc-4b1a-bb2a-2cd8b6e2155f"
    },
    {
      "_id": {
        "$oid": "60b889fe6a02f51e3cca53c4"
      },
      "question": "q",
      "answer": 2,
      "id": "250e4277-19b5-4bbb-81c8-fa6cce37a4f1"
    },
    {
      "_id": {
        "$oid": "60b889fe6a02f51e3cca53c5"
      },
      "question": "w",
      "answer": 3,
      "id": "ed5cc87d-f220-42f2-a873-1e7593bffd7d"
    },
    {
      "_id": {
        "$oid": "60b889fe6a02f51e3cca53c6"
      },
      "question": "w",
      "answer": 3,
      "id": "82ab720b-6e2f-4a28-8d41-77bd60ae572f"
    },
    {
      "_id": {
        "$oid": "60b889fe6a02f51e3cca53c7"
      },
      "question": "r",
      "answer": 5,
      "id": "5afcec9a-3153-4739-a88d-47a47a9d2ca5"
    }
  ],
  "id": "75074972-4c57-4fef-8e1b-612894de8ed0",
  "__v": 0
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "60b889fe6a02f51e3cca53c8"
  },
  "userId": "673hgf-7645u83-87653uf844495tr",
  "batchId": "10002",
  "timeAttendant": {
    "$date": "2021-06-03T07:51:26.484Z"
  },
  "attended": false,
  "comment": "i",
  "rating": [
    {
      "_id": {
        "$oid": "60b889fe6a02f51e3cca53c9"
      },
      "question": "p",
      "answer": 1,
      "id": "e8cb2464-5db0-499d-a29e-74fc1d244d72"
    },
    {
      "_id": {
        "$oid": "60b889fe6a02f51e3cca53ca"
      },
      "question": "j",
      "answer": 10,
      "id": "50df05c7-5c22-435f-9058-1ced3750ffba"
    },
    {
      "_id": {
        "$oid": "60b889fe6a02f51e3cca53cb"
      },
      "question": "h",
      "answer": 4,
      "id": "e338c840-be57-4c67-a76d-7b38efda1ea2"
    },
    {
      "_id": {
        "$oid": "60b889fe6a02f51e3cca53cc"
      },
      "question": "g",
      "answer": 4,
      "id": "d85b4bb7-789b-435b-8a05-545968bda16a"
    },
    {
      "_id": {
        "$oid": "60b889fe6a02f51e3cca53cd"
      },
      "question": "uy",
      "answer": 9,
      "id": "708f0aef-3abf-4a6f-9cc8-be111e602335"
    }
  ],
  "id": "76fc3345-17a2-4a4a-b2d4-2fa11483d6ac",
  "__v": 0
}]